In the Ghettos of Harlem you don't buy respect... you earn it.
Juice is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Ernest R. Dickerson.
Four Harlem friends -- Bishop, Q, Steel and Raheem -- dabble in petty crime,
but they decide to go big by knocking off a convenience store.
Bishop, the magnetic leader of the group, has the gun.
But Q has different aspirations.
He wants to be a DJ and happens to have a gig the night of the robbery.
Unfortunately for him, Bishop isn't willing to take no for
answer in a game where everything's for keeps.
Quincy 'Q' Powell, played by Omar Epps.
Roland Bishop, played by Tupac Shakur.
Raheem Porter, played by Khalil Kain.
Steel, played by Jermaine Hopkins.
Yolanda, played by Cindy Herron.
Trip, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Juice is a 1992 American crime thriller film directed by Ernest R.
Dickerson (in his directorial debut), written by Dickerson and Gerard Brown, and
starring Omar Epps, Tupac Shakur, Jermaine Hopkins, and Khalil Kain.
It follows four black youths growing up in Harlem, following their day-to-day activities, their
struggles with police misconduct, rival neighborhood gangs, and their families.
The film marked the first acting role for Epps, Kain, and Shakur.
It was shot in Harlem in 1991.
The film explores themes of rap music, hip-hop, street gang.
The tone is emotional and intense.